- And now, ladies
and gentlemen--
yes, that's right--
Elvis Presley.
(crowd screams)
(guitar strums)
- Ladies and gentlemen, could
I have your attention, please?
I'd like to tell you
that we're gonna do a
sad song for you.
This song here's one
of the saddest songs
we've ever heard.
(audience laughs)
It really tells
a story, friends.
Beautiful lyrics.
It goes something like this.
(guitar strums)
(crowd screams)
(crowd scream)
♪ You ain't nothin'
but a hound dog ♪
♪ Crying all the time ♪
♪ You ain't nothin'
but a hound dog ♪
♪ Cryin' all the time ♪
♪ Well, you ain't
never caught a rabbit ♪
♪ and you ain't no
friend of mine ♪
(crowd screams)
♪ Well they said you
was high-classed ♪
♪ Well, that was just a lie ♪
♪ You know they said
you was high-classed ♪
♪ Well, that was just a lie ♪
♪ Well, you ain't
never caught a rabbit ♪
♪ and you ain't no
friend of mine ♪
♪ You ain't nothin'
but a hound dog ♪
♪ Cryin' all the time ♪
♪ You ain't nothin'
but a hound dog ♪
♪ Cryin' all the time ♪
♪ Well, you ain't
never caught a rabbit ♪
♪ and you ain't no
friend of mine ♪
(crowd screams)
♪ Well, they said she
was high-classed ♪
♪ Well, that was just a lie ♪
♪ You know they said
you was high-classed ♪
♪ Well, that was just a lie ♪
♪ Well, you ain't
never caught a rabbit ♪
♪ and you ain't no
friend of mine ♪
(crowd screams)
♪ You ain't nothin'
but a hound dog ♪
♪ Cryin' all the time ♪
♪ You ain't nothin'
but a hound dog ♪
♪ Cryin' all the time ♪
♪ Well, you ain't
never caught a rabbit ♪
♪ you ain't no friend of mine ♪
(crowd screams)
- Thank you.
(crowd scream)
Ladies and gentlemen
I'd like to tell you, friends,
I'd like to tell you, please,
ladies and gentlemen,
I'd like to tell you
that on Thanksgiving Day
I think that our new
picture is to be released
and also we'll be back with
Mr. Ed Sullivan in January.
We'd like of millions of
wonderful people who
are watching in tonight, friends
and, I'd like to say this,
until we meet you again,
may God bless you,
as He's blessed me.
Thank you very much.
(crowd screams)